Contact

kd.boyles21@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/katrinadianne-boyles-bsn-rn-cpntncc-63617963 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Certified Pediatric Nurse Nursing Healthcare

Languages

Pampango/Kapampangan (Native or Bilingual)

Tagalog (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Trauma Nursing Core Course (TNCC) Certified

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

Katrina Dianne Boyles BSN, RN, CPN, TNCC

Pediatric Travel ER Registered Nurse Houston, Texas

Summary

Experienced Pediatric Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Home Care, Nursing, Customer Service, Hospitals, and Healthcare. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science in Nursing Degree.

Experience

Texas Children's Hospital
4 years 10 months
Pediatric ER Registered Nurse
June 2017 - Present (3 years 1 month)
Houston, Texas

Pediatric Acute Care Registered Nurse September 2015 - June 2017 (1 year 10 months) Katy, TX

CHOC Children's
Pediatric Travel ER Registered Nurse
November 2019 - April 2020 (6 months)
Orange County, California Area

MedCare Pediatric Group, LP
Pediatric Registered Nurse
August 2015 - September 2016 (1 year 2 months)
12371 S Kirkwood Rd, Stafford, TX 77477

Encompass Home Health & Hospice Pediatric Registered Nurse July 2013 - September 2015 (2 years 3 months) Seton Healthcare Family Cardiology Registered Nurse February 2013 - September 2013 (8 months)

1201 W. 38th St., Austin, TX 78705

West Houston Medical Center
Telemetry Registered Nurse
June 2011 - February 2013 (1 year 9 months)
12141 Richmond Avenue, Houston, TX

Allied Home Health Services Certified Nursing Assistant August 2009 - June 2011 (1 year 11 months) Houston, Texas

The Concierge: Luxury Healthcare and Rehabilitation Center Certified Nursing Assistant
August 2008 - January 2010 (1 year 6 months)
Houston, Texas

Brilliant Care Home Caregiver April 2007 - April 2007 (1 month) Chandler, Arizona

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington

Master of Science in Nursing, Pediatric Nurse Practitioner · (2018 - 2021)

The University of Texas at Arlington

Bachelor of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2015 - 2017)

Houston Community College
Associate's Degree in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2008 - 2011)